



Esat Can Gök

• Work: 6312 Zabriskie Ln, Death Valley, CA 92328, Amerika Birleşik Devletleri, 531-622-9899, 2600, United States

Email: gokesatcan1@gmail.com **Phone:** (+90) 5316229899

○ WhatsApp Messenger: +90 5316229899

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/esat-can-gök-0555a923b/?

originalSubdomain=tr

Gender: Male **Date of birth:** 04/09/2003 **Nationality:** Turkish

ABOUT ME

Since I realized that software and computer technologies are the most important shaping factors in the changing world order, my aim is not only to be an engineer, but to develop myself as an engineer who thinks differently, is a researcher and can produce solutions even in the most difficult conditions when necessary. I am happy to share all my savings that I have learned and experienced in this process. I fully believe that positive direction and effective use of developing technology is the best solution to increase absolute prosperity for our country, nation and humanity.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[15/03/2022 - 14/11/2023] **Software engineer**

DataKritik Software and Consultancy https://datakritik.com/

City: Ankara | **Country:** Türkiye

-earthquake detection systems

-object oriented programming

-mobile applications

-Unmanned Aerial Vehicles Control Systems

-Unmanned Aerial Vehicles Communication Systems

[01/05/2023 - 30/05/2023]

Competition Manager

Teknofest T3 Foundation https://www.t3vakfi.org/tr/

City: Istanbul | Country: Türkiye

-unmanned submarine vehicle control

-unmanned submarine vehicles technical support

[04/09/2021 - 13/08/2022]

Software engineer

BlackNight UAV Team (attempt)

City: Karabuk | Country: Türkiye

-vertical take-off unmanned aerial vehicle mission software

-vertical take-off unmanned aerial vehicle control and communication software

-team leadership

[15/10/2022 - 22/05/2024] **Application software developer**

MILITEK

City: Karabuk | Country: Türkiye

- Mobile Application Developer
- -Object Detection Software Developer (AI)

[15/03/2023 - 15/06/2023]

Sales Consultant

LcWaikiki https://corporate.lcwaikiki.com/

- Sales Consultant
- -Warehouse organization and stock control

(Earthquake happened in Turkey so I was a student and I need money for my family)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

EDUCATION AND TRAIN-ING

[04/09/2021 - Current] Bachelor Degree

University of Karabuk https://www.karabuk.edu.tr/

City: Karabuk | **Field(s) of study:** Engineering, manufacturing and construction

• Computer Engineering (Computer Science)

[04/09/2022 – Current]

Bachelor Degree

Istanbul University https://www.istanbul.edu.tr/tr

City: Istanbul

PROJECTS

[04/08/2021 – Current] Unmanned Aerial Vehicles Ground Control System

-Pixhawk is a collective control software with an advanced network and server infrastructure that allows communication, control and tracking of all card-supported fixed wing and rotary wing aircraft. Officially used and tested. Due to project confidentiality and rights, sharing can only be done face to face.

[15/01/2023 – 22/10/2023] Earthquake Detection and Urban Evacuation Planning Ecosystem (ZELZELE)

-Electronic devices and artificial intelligence-supported software have been built to ensure communication of the earthquake-detected area and to instantly draw evacuation and aid routes according to the direction of collapsed buildings. The project came second in Teknofest International Technology Competitions in Turkey. It was broadcast on many news channels. It is starting to be actively used in Turkey.

Link: https://www.trthaber.com/haber/bilim-teknoloji/iskenderunlu-depremzedeogrenciler-zelzele-ile-hasari-anlik-tespit-edecek-763691.html

[01/01/2024 - 20/05/2024] **EPITECH**

-It is a system developed to enable epilepsy patients to drive. If the patient loses consciousness in an emergency, the vehicle will park autonomously and safely (Image processing and control). Then he will call the emergency team.

[01/01/2024 – Current] **Medtermo**

Electrical media provider for medicines that require storage at a specific temperature. Control and monitoring can be done with the mobile application.

Link: https://www.teknofest.org/tr/competitions/competition_report_detail/2317